Contact: turkision@gmail.com
White. We're looking for a white flower.
Oh no! Not here. Not here!
Have a good look, Cerkutay Bey.
Look here. Does it look like this?
Not this.
-What about this?
-No, no. Not that one either.
Remember, Cerkutay. Remember.
We're digging with a needle, Alaattin
Bey. My sister won't be able to survive.
Do we have another thing to
do, Mehmed Bey? I told you.
I tried everything, but it
didn't work. We have to find it.
We need to look faster. Come on!
It looked like this. Like this.
Like this. Not exactly this.
Something with more flowers.
I know it from my childhood.
They said it could heal everything.
You are talking about heliotrope.
It's heliotrope. We can find it around here.
Split up now. Meet me near the horses later.
You say that's the heal? My sister will live.
She will live, with Allah's will.
We will find it. We will.
If you hadn't shot that dog, none
of these would have happened.
You are the reason why they tried to kill me,
...why Jandar Bey got killed
and my daughter got shot, Osman!
For years, you have given
this land nothing but suffering.
-You and your house!
-Enough!
Enough, Yakup Bey!
When you ignore the
enemy, they won't disappear!
When you neglect the war
the peace won't be ours!
You blame our own kin for the
every move the enemy makes.
This is enough.
-Osman Bey.
-This is the war of the right and the wrong!
It has been going on for a thousand years
and will continue for a thousand yealrs
And Islam will be the winner of this war.
But you should know this.
I will crush whoever gets in our way.
We will fight Mongolians.
Is your head...
...too heavy for your shoulders?
How dare you talk to me like this?
Stop.
Osman Bey is right!
Osman Bey is right.
Our ancestors escaped from
them and came to this land.
Many generations have been wasted
during the battles and the journey.
We have nowhere else left to go!
Nowhere, Yakup Bey.
It is the war of survival now.
For this reason, Osman Bey is right.
There is no point in blaming Osman Bey.
We should just do what he says.
Being a sultan means listening
to the right man in hard times.
Let's see, Yakup Bey.
I listen to the words of my beys.
What will we do now, Osman Bey?
We will turn these lands
where the beys and alps died...
...into a homeland. And
we will protect them forever.
Let's go.
There some people coming.
What are you doing here, Turks?
You wait. You need to look for the heal.
-My sister will live.
-My Shahzade.
Gokmen, you too.
You can't fight alone, Mehmed Bey.
You can't even imagine what
I can do alone, Alaattin Bey.
Especially what I can do for my sister.
You make people live. I make people die.
-Go!
Let's go.
Come on.
-Come here, dogs.
-Attack!
Alps, take position!
Father!
Let's go, my Bey! Come!
-Father, are you alright?
-I'm good. I'm good.
-You?
-I'm fine, thanks to Allah.
They can't resist.
Shoot, Erlik Khan's nokers!
They're determined to kill us today, my Sultan.
I won't die today until I see my daughter!
-We'll reach the frontier market.
-Yes, we will.
We will, Yakup Bey.
-Konur, attack when the arrows stop.
-As you order, my Bey.
Heliotrope. Found beside briars.
Come on Alaeddin, come
on. Find it already, come on.
Come on.
Come forward you dogs. You
never have enough of dying.
Heliotrope, thank Allah.
Thank Allah. Its heliotrope.
Thank Allah. Thank you my Rabb.
However, it is not enough.
Another, more.
Ya Fattah, Al Fattah.
Thank Allah. Thank you my Rabb.
I will catch up. Hold on a little longer.
-Saadet Hatun.
-Bala, she is burning.
Alaeddin said ice would be
good. The girls got it ready.
Fitnat, Kismet bring the ice.
Quickly now.
-Gonca.
-It just came, we also gave it to others.
Quickly.
Ya Fattah.
What did you resist for? All
of you meet the same end.
-You go after the others.
-You do not know me.
Every second I gain will
help healing my sister.
Hold on a little longer. Thank Allah.
I found it! I found it!
I found it!
-Thank Allah, I've found it!
-Thank Allah.
-Is this it, Cerkutay Bey?
-This is it.
We need to go to the
marketplace quickly, come on.
My Bey, you have poison in your
blood, and Yakup Bey's daughter.
-You need to get to frontier marketplace.
-This will not be a retreat.
-Never Bey, no more escaping.
-You will repulse them.
Then you will draw them to
the forest and end them all.
-As you command, Bey.
-Attack!
-Now!
-Come on!
Yakup Bey, come on!
Alps, fall back to the forest.
Neither them nor us
will get out of this forest..
Until they reach the
marketplace and find an antidote.
Come on, Alps!
Hold on my son, my valiant.
Your father will save you.
My Bey is a martyr now. He is a martyr now.
Don't take him. My Cemal, where are you going?
He is strong like his father, right?
You waited with me for all these years.
Now when you just united with your father..
When you just called him
"father", do not go, alright?
Ulgen, don't do this. Don't lose hope.
-He will be alright, if Allah permits.
-If Allah permits.
Bala.
How did you endure this pain?
It is a test.
HE gives life and HE takes it. What can I say.
This world is temporary.
I keep my longing secret in my family.
Come on.
Attack! They have poison in their blood!
Now the ground will have them!
They will not get out of this forest!
We will see who won't get out of this forest.
Come on.
These lands have been graves for many tyrants.
Now it is your time you corrupt dog!
Cheer up the dark spirits! Attack!
Do you think I would go after
them without protecting my back?
You will all die.
Konur Bey, these dogs has trapped us.
-We won't hold.
-Alps.
Fall back to the forest. Cover my back.
Soldiers, attack!
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
-Osman.
-My Bala.
Yakup Bey, where were you!
Yakup Bey, my Gonca is
going, my daughter is fading.
-Where is my Gonca?
-Inside.
-Did Alaeddin find a cure?
They are still looking for it.
Cerkutay remembered something. They
went to look for some weed on the hills.
-We do not have much time, I am afraid.
-My son will find it.
-He will find it.
-I hope so.
Mother Bala. My father.
Osman. Did you also..
No, I am alright.
I am alright.
He got shot by a poison
arrow, it is effecting quickly.
It is bruised. My Allah, protect him.
-Osman.
-My Bala, I am alright.
Do not worry.
My Orhan, you go to the tent.
I will prepare a balm, until Alaeddin comes.
-It will slow the poison.
-Do not worry.
-Come on.
My son... Don't say anything to anyone for now.
Father... Don't... You are tiring yourself.
Don't worry, my son. I am alright.
I am alright. Come on.
I'll resist until the ointment is
brought here. Come on, walk.
They took the bait! Osman
Bey's way is now open!
Come on Alps!
They will soon see the strength of my soul.
I will crush this soil in such a way that
every plant that grows will be crooked.
The situation is not good, my Bey. Most
of those who were injured became martyrs.
Osman! -No...
-Osman, are you alright?
-They will all pay for it.
My father was injured.
-He was injured?
Osman! Make him sit down!
Osman! My Osman!
-My Allah, protect him!
-Alaeddin, my son...
Osman! My Allah, protect him!
Father! -Welcome, father!
Father! Father, are you alright?
My daughter...
Father.. -Fatma, don't worry.
Come on! Come on, carry him!
-Come on!
-O Allah!
-Let's lay him down!
Slowly! My Osman!
Osman!
Come on! -Here... Slowly.
My angel.. My daughter...
Open your eyes, my beautiful Gonca...
What if she does not wake up, Yakup Bey?
I will not surrender my
daughter to this little wound.
My daughter is strong. She will be alright.
I will bring healers from all around.
No...
Alaeddin Bey talked to all of them.
No one has witnessed this poison before.
I will punish them.
I will rip the hearts of
those who hurt my daughter.
My Gonca..
Ya Shafi... Ya Shafi...
Ya Shafi...
The poison is spreading.
My Allah, let him stay
with us. Please, protect him.
Ya Shafi...
BismillahirRahmaniRahim.
Father, open your eyes...
Mother.. Mother, say something.
My daughter.. Look at me.
Nothing will happen to your father.
Your father is a strong
man. Pull yourself together.
Nothing will happen to him.
Come on brother... Where have you been?
He is having a temperature.
Kismet. Let's prepare
ice and water with vinegar.
Ya Shafi... Ya Shafi...
Ulgen! Ulgen! Ulgen!
We found the herb I remembered.
Alaeddin Bey also knew it.
Our son will survive.
Will it take long, Alaeddin Bey?
-No.
We will take it when it boils.
BismillahirRahmaniRahim.
Alaeddin... My son did you find it?
We did, mother. We did, thanks to Allah.
Cerkutay Bey...
Mother... Mother, what happened to you?
Did... Did Gonca Hatun...
My sister? Bala Hatun?
-It's not Gonca.
Gonca is still unconscious, but...
Your father... Osman Bey was also poisoned.
My father?
My Bey...
You go. Tell us what to do.
Kismet Hatun. Crush the
other plants and boil them.
Make everyone drink it when
it is warm after distilling it.
Yes my Shahzade. -Come on!
Come on!
People! The shifa was found!
We found it, Boran Bey. We found the shifa.
My Allah... Let him stay with us...
My father is strong. He will
get better with Allah's consent.
He will get better.
Father! -Alaeddin...
-Brother.
Did you find the cure?
-I did, brother.
-Thanks to my Allah!
-My brother, you arrived...
...you will heal
my father, right?
He will survive,
my sister. He will.
My Alaeddin, come on.
Father... You will get better.
You will get better if Allah permits.
You will get better.
Alaeddin Bey. It is now warm.
Come on. -Brother..
Make him stand.
BismillahirRahmaniRahim.
Ya Shafi... Ya Shafi..
Ya Shafi...
May it heal him if Allah permits...
-If Allah permits...
-Slowly... slowly...
My son... It will work, right?
-He will get better if Allah permits.
-He will.
You will get better with Allah's
consent. Wake up, my Bey..
I am here, sister! I arrived.
-My lion son..
-Thanks to Allah...
-My Gonca...
-BismillahirRahmaniRahim.
Ya Shafi... Ya Shafi...
Drink it, my daughter...
-Ya Shafi...
Cerkutay... Hold his head.
Come on, my son...
Come on, my valiant...
BismillahirRahmaniRahim
Ya Shafi...
-You will get better.
-Thank you...
Nokers must be after us now.
-Konur Bey, they are coming.
-Aykurt, come on.
They're here, be careful.
The jackal who enters the
wolf's den will end up dying.
You'll be the ones to die!
Your rule in these lands
is over. You'll die soon.
You can never rule in these lands.
Tell me, where is your leader?
Konur Bey. Konur Bey.
This pain will not end if you don't talk.
You cannot hurt Karacelasun.
I have eyes on everywhere.
Speak.
I said speak.
He will be in the inn in the east. He'll
kill you even if you attack him. Go and die.
The one who sees himself over
everyone goes blind. We will kill him too.
Alps, go to the horses. We'll
go to Osman Bey quickly.
Come on sister, open your eyes.
-Mother.
-Gonca.
-My sister is waking up mother.
Gonca, thankfully. My Gonca.
-Mother.
-Gonca.
-Sister.
-Thankfully.
Father.
Thankfully.
-Thankfully. My daughter...
-Gonca.
Thankfully. My beautiful daughter.
-May I come in?
-Come on in.
Gonca Hatun is finally awake.
-Thank you my Allah.
-Thankfully.
-Thanks to Rabb.
If Allah permits my Bey will also wake up.
Osman?
-Osman.
-My Bey.
My Bey!
My Allah, thank you! Thank you my Allah.
Osman?
Thankfully.
He's awake.
Did you think you can get rid of me so easily?
Thankfully.
My Bey? Are you all right?
-I'm all right.
-Do you have any pain?
Of course you'd be all right. Osman
Bey wouldn't fall because of an arrow.
Thankfully.
One risked his life
and the other one the other one...
...did his best to find a cure.
Thank you all.
And the other one keeps praying.
Shush. Don't cry anymore.
-I'm all right. I'm all right.
-Thankfully.
Come on boy.
Mother.
Son?
My brave boy! My boy.
My Allah, thank you!
I couldn't sleep well because of you.
Cerkutay Bey, are you crying?
A man does not cry.
I don't know whether a man cries or not
but fathers cry, son.
-Mother.
-Yes, son?
-Am I Ghazi (veteran) now?
-Ghazi?
Yes, you are Ghazi.
Ulgen.
You know, you would say that I will name him.
Your name is Ghazi from now on.
-Is my name Ghazi from now on?
-Ghazi Alp.
Kiss your mother's hand.
-I'm Ghazi now.
-You are Ghazi.
Cerkutay Bey, Sultan Yakup is waiting for you.
Now, get some rest son.
What's going on?
-Mother.
-Honey.
-I'm Ghazi, right, mother?
-Yes, dear.
Give me patience my Allah!
My Bey is struggling with plenty of things.
Mongolian pagans on
one side, crusading infidels
on the other, and
poison on top of that...
Tawba Astagfirullah. We
couldn't even find the traitor.
Don't worry my Bey, he will
eventually give himself away.
He will, and then we will hunt him down.
-He can't hide forever after all.
-Yes, he can't.
Brother, I've been meaning
to ask you for a while.
I forgot in my haste, I'm sorry.
Your father was sick, right? How did it happen?
My father is all right.
He is all right, Alhamdulillah. Shahzade's
medicine worked well, thankfully.
Praise be, thankfully.
-Thank you.
-Veysel.
How are your parents?
My father was martyred during
the conquest of Inegol, my Bey.
-May Allah rest his soul.
-May Allah bless you.
I have an old mother, praying for your health.
MashaAllah. May Allah give her a long life.
-Aameen.
-Is she in Yenisehir?
No, my Bey. She's in the
countryside, in Tepekoy.
Tepekoy. Right, I know it.
Visit her every once in a
while, don't leave her alone.
Don't neglect her because of your duty.
Okay my Bey. I'll do as you order.
Good news. Bayindir Bey,
the cure has been found.
-Thank you my Rabb!
-Alhamdulillah.
Thankfully! Thankfully.
-My Bey, let me continue
with the inspection.
Right.
-Continue.
-Thank you.
Let's go to the house he talked about tomorrow.
Let's see if he's telling the truth or not.
Do you suspect Veysel?
I would even suspect myself
if I didn't know what I was doing.
Your son is well, right, Cerkutay?
He's good, my Sultan.
-Thanks to Allah.
-Praise be!
Praise be.
Who shot your son Cerkutay?
Mongolians shot him, my Sultan.
Who made Mongolians mess with us?
Osman Bey, my Sultan.
Good. Good.
You see the truth.
-And you'll do your duty properly.
-Always.
My Sultan, as you order.
Now go back to Osman Bey.
But your loyalty will be just for me.
You will stand beside him...
...so we won't get in such troubles again.
And our children won't be hurt.
I was going to lose my child too, Cerkutay.
We were going to have the same suffering.
-We will prevent this.
-My Sultan.
You can ask me to do everything, but...
-Osman Bey...
-Don't, Cerkutay. Don't.
Don't you try to question my orders.
Don't you ever disobey me.
Never forget...
...who saved you...
...and who gave you freedom.
You will be with Osman.
You will be his best man like the old days.
And you will let me know
about every move of his.
As you order, my Sultan.
We'll stop them before they reach Tepekoy.
Otherwise, I'll have to let them meet Vasillis.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
They hurt us a lot, Osman Bey.
They couldn't even shave our beard.
Don't be worrying. We'll take their hearts out.
You encouraged the beys.
But this is just a dream.
-How can we stand against Olcaytu Khan?
-Yakup Bey.
I tell my alps about 40 warriors of Gokturk.
You say you are a sultan...
Don't make me talk about it.
You hear the epic Turks made
with blood not just a dream from me.
What happened to those warriors?
Who did they get killed?
Because they had a khan...
...who was having dreams beyond his power.
You're right, Yakup Bey.
Those who don't dream neither die
nor achieve. We have decided to achieve.
We will prevail with Allah's will.
Open the map, Mehmed. Let's see the situation.
Let's see what epics
Osman Bey will have for us.
We wore them out. We captured their castles.
Lords are afraid of us, but...
...Byzantine is still there.
Don't forget the Crusades, Osman.
Don't cross the line.
We can't fight in two fronts.
If Pope makes a call for help
...we will be stuck between
two armies and be destroyed.
You're right.
Because the army of Olcaytu
Khan we want to rise against...
...is twice as big as Byzantine.
We are actually having a
dream for the impossible.
But those without courage
will never understand us.
For sure, we have courage.
Yakup Bey, with or without you...
...we will establish the free state.
I'm happy that we've survived a great disaster.
Thanks, beauty. We are all happy.
Thanks, Holofira. But you seem so upset.
I'm good. My horses died during the raid.
Sorry about that, Holofira.
I know it's not easy.
Gonca Hatun, have you become a ghazi too?
Yes. I've become a ghazi too, Cerkutay Alp.
Well, my name is Ghazi now.
-Ghazi? Ulgen?
-Yes.
His name is Ghazi now. His father...
You have a real name now,
huh, Ghazi Alp? May it be blessed.
My dear.
I'm a ghazi now. Will you
marry me, Gonca Hatun?
Shut up! Shame on you!
You need to ask for the girl
from her mother first, Ghazi Alp.
You need to see what her parents think.
Saadet Hatun!
Will you give me Gonca to marry?
Let me kiss your hand if you do!
I don't know. My daughter may
have someone else in her heart, huh?
-We need to ask Gonca first.
-Get down here.
-Do you?
-Be quiet!
You need to grow up first, Ghazi
Alp. Marriage is not a child's game.
It has a heavy burden. You are too young.
Your shoulders can't carry this heavy burden.
You will find your match, if Allah permits.
Then you stop growing up, Gonca Hatun.
I'll grow older and we can get married!
My Allah! You're speaking
madly! Oh, did you bite me?
I'm sorry. I think the
poison affected his mouth.
-My Bey, do I have permission?
-Come, son.
If the Mongolian army
comes with the siege weapons,
...they will use these routes.
They are easy to hold.
A hundred men can stall
even a thousand for days.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
You are talking good.
But you are talking wrong, Orhan Bey.
If they come for destroying
instead of capturing,
...they will pass over the huge mountain
and come down on us as thousands.
The army will not come.
If it were to come, it would've by now.
Their intention is to make us powerless.
They will hit the caravans, they
will hit the Beys and marketplaces.
They will even hit Sultans.
Their intention is to have
the alps away from the war.
-Then what?
-Then the army will come.
However, it is clear what to do.
Now, we will have a feast in Yenisehir.
We will make a festival.
Osman Bey. We are having a war council.
We're saying that trouble
comes in two different ways.
And you leave the council
saying "We will have a feast".
So, Yakup Bey. Don't you
think they will hear about it?
Won't they say; "We are
hitting them from all sides."
"However, muslims' joy does not falter."
Their intention is to break our
spirits. We will not be broken.
Yakup Bey. You are also invited.
No, keep it.
Alright.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Send word to all frontier marketplace.
-If anyone wants to come, they are welcomed.
-As my Bey commands.
Yakup Bey. You send word to Beys.
Have them ready the armies.
First, we will stand up at the table.
Then, We will deal them the biggest blow.
Stay safe now.
Mother, open up. We are friends of Veysel.
Bayindir, you are looking for trouble. Don't.
Tell yourself she is missing and walk away.
-What do you command us to do, Bayindir Bey?
-Open it, brother.
Okay.
Those who wander in wrong
places bound to fall in every trap.
That corrupt dog. For how
long was he eating with us.
We noticed it late. Very late.
-We're starting.
-Alright, move.
Who were you looking for?
There is only death for you here.
I know very well about
what you call "treachery".
Precaution is our faithful friend. Alps!
In this deal, everyone can
get everything they want.
Since you want death you are welcomed.
-Come on!
-O Allah!
Damn it.
They know me now.
The palace duty is over for me.
-Saadet Hatun.
-Bala Hatun.
Osman Bey is inviting
everyone to the feast at evening.
-We would like to see you among us.
-Thank you, Bala Hatun.
I will talk with Yakup Bey, and let you know.
Bala Hatun is acting very
close to us, right Gonca?
Gonca, come here.
-Did you bury my horse?
They buried it
with other horses.
Don't be sad my lady. You will be sick.
Do not worry, I am alright.
You can get back to your duty.
Holofira.
Hope you are alright.
Sorry, we could not take care of you.
As you know the situation, my sister.
I am alright, thank you. As you can see.
I can see alright. You
are like a drop of water.
-Gonca, how is she?
-Thank Allah, she is alright.
However, now I think about
you. Those dogs killed your horse.
You can not hide your
pain. I know how hard it is.
I also put my horse Akkiremit way back.
My pain is fresh. However, it will pass.
I will get used to it for sure, thank you.
Your tears hurt my heart.
Do not be sad, Holofira.
I know it won't replace your horse, however..
I would like to gift you a horse.
That is very thoughtful of
you. But I have to decline.
If I would need a horse I can
buy it myself, I do not need you.
Thank you.
When I take Holofira from your
hands, you will be very hurt, Orhan.
My Gonca. Get prepared.
You will go to Osman Bey's invitation as well.
Mother, didn't father told us to not go?
We won't go, you will.
-Mother, what will I do there alone?
-My Gonca.
You will be our eyes and ears in that palace.
Stay alert. Osman will not just sit around.
-As you command, mother.
-You'll know what to do.
My Allah.
Where did I put that handkerchief?
Holofira.
That's why I don't want you to come
to marketplace, Mehmed is on your tail.
Still, you told him alright.
Right? And what did you do, Orhan?
While your mother announces
the bride she has chosen for you?
What was her name.. Aysima.
While she can not tell them
enough, what did you do, Orhan?
Holofira.
Since I declared my love to you..
I don't care what my mother says or wants.
For me, there is only you, lord's daughter.
-May it be easy.
-Sister.
Holofira, we're doing a feast in palace
at evening, my father expects you.
As we know what you
did for my brother at Kestel.
We want to thank you.
You will come, lord's daughter?
Aysima, my daughter. We expect
you at Yenisehir in the evening.
-Yenisehir?
We're having a feast at
the palace, you're welcomed.
As you wish, Malhun Hatun.
Alps are ready, Malhun Hatun.
-All right.
Come on daughter, don't be late.
-May I come in my Bey?
-Come on in.
-My Bey.
-Did you find him, Bayindir?
I did, my Bey.
-But I couldn't bring him before you.
-Who is he?
Dastard Veysel.
Even his name is not Veysel.
He is working for Crusaders.
I went to his house to confirm what he said.
We were ambushed there, that's why he escaped.
We were ambushed there that's why he escaped.
You're all right, that's the important thing.
We've been looking for that traitor for
a long time but no one could find him.
Well done. Well done,
you have shown your skills.
Thank you my Bey. Thank you, but
I couldn't finish it.
You will finish it eventually.
But be careful
do not let Yakup Bey take advantage of it.
If he gets this opportunity
He will definitely use it against us.
Get this done quickly.
-Yes, my Bey.
-May I come in my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey.
I couldn't kill Karacelasun.
-But I know where he is.
-Alright.
Alright, but...
...tell me, you gain victory
but you are hesitant to say it.
Why are you acting like this?
We will raise now.
Don't bow your heads we will stand.
This is how soldiers of Islam should be.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
Alps will be ready in the morning.
Bows, arrows, spears, everything will be ready.
But no need for plenty of
men, pick the best ones.
Yes, my Bey.
And the most daring one
will be leading them.
It tastes great. Take it.
Gonca, daughter, you just
got up, do not tire yourself.
Of course not, Bala Hatun. I can't
slack while everyone else is working.
Praise be. But do not tire yourself out.
All right.
You always keep Gonca with you.
I'm trying to get to know her
to see if she's like her mother
or is she who she seems to be?
Malhun.
But I liked Aysima a lot.
She's well-mannered and beautiful.
She's also strong, we've
seen her skills during the raid.
It will be done when Orhan says yes.
-If Allah permits!
-Come on.
Speak of the devil.
-Welcome, daughter.
-Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
I didn't want to approach as
you were busy this morning.
I hope it gets better soon, and I made halwa.
Thank you, daughter. You did very well.
My Orhan loves halwa.
Sisters, bring plates, come on.
Aysima?
-What are you doing here?
-Thank you, Gonca Hatun.
So you know each other?
Very well. Very well.
We want her to be the bride of
my Orhan if it's meant to be like that.
Orhan?
Whoever I wish for, he comes. Come here.
Where do you think you're going. Come.
Aysima brought us halwa.
I said my Orhan loves it and then you appeared.
-Right?
-Yes, that's right.
Daughter, give Orhan a
plate of halwa, let him taste it.
Mother, how many times
more do I have to tell you?
I do not want it. Why do you trying so hard?
Orhan, I'm not telling you to marry.
But get to know her, don't
you care for your mother at all?
-Why would I get to know her?
-Orhan.
Do not make me repeat myself, come on.
Come on.
Sisters, come on.
Fatma, Gonca, come on daughter.
Come on.
-Enjoy your food, Orhan Bey.
-Thank you, Aysima Hatun, but,
-I'm full.
-It's a dessert, after all.
But if you don't want it..
Do you like it?
Thank you, it tastes well.
Enjoy it.
Thank you, that's enough for me.
It tastes very well, thank you.
They've seen you, ma'am,
you need to stay strong.
If they want to play games,
then I'll play.
-Enjoy it.
-Holofira?
Everyone is here.
We're late, Andra.
-I'm so happy to see you well, Gonca.
-Thank you, Holofira.
Welcome, Holofira, but you shouldn't
have bothered all the way here.
-You're a guest.
-Mother.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
We've never met.
I'm Aysima.
Nice to meet you a lot.
Holofira.
If everything is ready,
let's go to the council.
Brother... Here.
Drink.
Apparently, tonight will be
very difficult for you, brother.
Stop there, my sister. Stop.
Ah mother... Ah... You did this to me.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Father... I am embarrassed.
But this happened although
we took strict precautions.
Mehmet... You did your duty well, my son.
Besides, we are struggling
with Mongols because of Osman.
How can he be a hero?
First, he must answer for that.
You must see the result, Hatun.
All Beys are asking for a fight.
Many things happen but..
...Osman gains the most every time.
What do you mean, Yakup Bey?
Do you think it is Osman's game?
-We'll see, Hatun.
We'll see.
Cerkutay will now stand next to Osman.
But... he will serve us.
If Osman gets over him and...
...makes another plan...
...there will be bloodshed.
Then...
...it will be a shame for my lands.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Cerkutay.
My Bey...
I do not want to stay away from you anymore.
If you allow me, I want to gather my family..
...and come back to my lands, my Bey.
There is always a room
for you here, don't worry.
Of course, we will find
a suitable duty for you.
Come on. Have some rest now.
I had... I had
enough rest, my Bey.
I did.
Now allow me to fight.
Praise be to my valiant.
This is my valiant.
Now Osman will die...
I will have taken my brother's revenge...
Even meat tastes better now.
Taste. -I haven't taken my revenge yet.
Before I send those barbarians
away from these heavenly lands...
...I cannot find peace.
Where are your men?
Apparently Osman killed them.
What if they told him your location?
Good then. Osman will come
to me to get himself killed.
Crusader's man came.
Let him in.
Vasilis..
Osman and Yakup's daughter are alive.
It was impossible for them to
survive after being poisoned!
How did that happen?
-Not only that...
I was exposed, Master Gera.
Bayindir noticed me.
Come on now.
BismillahirRahmaniRahim.
Here. -BismillahirRahmaniRahim.
Gonca, my daughter...
You did well by coming here.
Thank you Bala Hatun.
I mean all of you...
You did well by coming here.
Praise be to my beautiful daughters.
Aysima is Kasim Bey's daughter, Osman Bey.
She saved my life during the raid.
Praise be. Praise be.
Thank you, my daughter.
Not at all, Malhun Hatun.
Anyone would do the same.
They are all at their marrying age. Praise be!
But they are single.
Osman Bey will not approve this.
Who am I? That's what our
Rasulullah Efendi (PBUH) said.
When it is time, you should not delay it.
Right... Right Gonca Hatun?
Gonca Hatun will not get married!
She is waiting for me to
grow up! Don't you dare!
Oh is she? -Ghazi...
Shut up... You disgraced us.
Why would I? It's love! I was being honest!
Speak, my lion. We are supporting you!
I said my words, I forgot the rest!
-Now it is enough!
-O praise be!
Ghazi.. Ghazi...
Ghazi... eat your food come on, my lion.
Alaeddin... You couldn't even be as brave
as this little boy, keep watching there.
Ghazi will grow up and ask
Gonca Hatun before you...
...then you'll see.
Do you think it is easy? Besides...
...look at yourself before talking about me.
You are right.
So my Cerkutay.. Tell me.
Are you doing something to heal your hand?
I... am not doing anything, my Bey.
I accepted it. I bowed down.
-Why are you saying that?
Boran! -My Bey.
-Bring those here.
Yes my Bey. -My Bey...
What will he bring? -The entrustment.
After what you said...
...then the things that will heal you...
...are these swords.
-My Bey... I don't want them.
-I did not ask you.
Come on, hold them.
Those were entrusted to you.
Those were entrusted
to you by Bamsi Bey.
We did not dismiss you
from your duty, Cerkutay.
Thank you my Bey.
There is no need to make
Sultan mad. Still, do your duty.
Yes my Bey. -Come on then.
So that we are having a good day...
...Boran. -My Bey.
Play your qopuz.
Yes my Bey.
My Bey...
Come on. You may sit.
Your man is not saying
any good words, Crusader.
Since no one died...
...this attack will gather Turks.
They can all gather and embrace each other...
...I can still kill Osman
and Yakup, all of them!
Then what? Your greed must not blind you.
Their children, commanders, Alps...
They will all unite and attack us.
I will not hesitate attacking them even
if I stand against a thousand people.
I will not stop even if my sword is broken.
-You will, Mongol.
Because they will kill each other.
What is the fox in your
head saying again, Crusader?
So that our brother Vasilis was exposed...
...I will use him in such a way that...
But I need the poison you used.
Vasilis... You will take shelter in Yakup.
You will do it with this poison in your hand.
We deceived Osman for years.
Now it's Yakup's turn.
Yakup's turn.
He will convince Yakup
that I allied with Osman, huh?
Good. But we can't do this only with you.
They'll catch a noker.
He will tell the same story.
You both will tell Yakup that Osman came to me.
Then Yakup will have to believe.
They will drown in their own blood.
Mother, I told you I didn't want her
but you brought her to the palace!
I can't, mother! I can't.
You're giving her false hopes.
Don't you care about her feelings?
Mother.
Here... There is someone.
Both my mind and heart say the same.
They say Holofira.
Understand me already.
Enough, Orhan! You aren't a child.
You can't be with Holofira! Your
heart can't see. What about your eyes?
Are they blind too? Is Holofira a Muslim?
What if she becomes a Muslim?
Will you let me then, mother?
You think that's the only problem?
She grew up in luxury. That
girl can't endure hardships.
Would she carry your burden? Tell me.
If you say she would, I will keep quiet then.
What's going on?
We're talking about Orhan's
future marriage, my Bey.
You can talk later.
Make your preparations.
You will lead the best warriors.
We will kill Karacelasun.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Come on.
What is it? You look angry.
As long as Holofira is here,
he won't want another girl.
My hands are tied up. I don't know what to do.
Just be patient. He will see what is right.
I hope so, my Bey. I can't
stand seeing my son suffering.
And this is Shahzade Alaattin's room.
He lets only me go inside.
Yes?
Then you know Scholar's all secrets. Ha, Ghazi?
Of course I do.
You also know, Gonca Hatun.
-I know what?
-My secrets.
-I was just walking around.
When Fatma saw me...
There is nothing
to be a secret.
This is my world. Anyone
curious can look inside.
You read poems. I know that.
Do you write?
I do. I write, but...
...I don't leave them around.
You know what? The daisies I gave you...
-Did you drink?
-No.
-I just threw them away.
-You did?
You threw them away?
That's why your anger still stands here.
During the training, I realized
that you'd have cut me if you could.
I can, but...
But what?
You don't want to hurt me?
Gonca.
I owe you more lives now, Alaattin Bey.
You owe me nothing, Trickster Hatun.
-Only if you didn't call me that.
-What would you do then?
Gonca.
I will tell you something.
-I...
-My Shahzade.
I'm coming.
Excuse me.
My Shahzade, Osman Bey
will go to Karacelasun at dawn.
He wants you to determine the route.
How many people will he go
with? I will draw a route accordingly.
My Bey wants to keep it secret. We'll
be just a few. Nobody should know.
Alright. Let's go.
A night has passed and there
is still no news from Orhan Bey.
I can't stand it anymore. We
need to go as soon as possible.
Holofira.
-What do you want?
-Can we talk in privacy?
I think you got in the wrong way.
If you want halvah, the kitchen is in the back.
Holofira, look.
I'm here to talk about this matter.
I'm all innocent in this matter.
But I don't have much time. If you hear me...
You don't have much time?
You think about me just now,
Orhan? I couldn't sleep all night.
Me neither.
I didn't sleep all night either, Holofira.
I always thought about you.
But I wanted your anger to cool off.
You disappointed me, Orhan.
-When I saw you like that...
-I brought this...
...to heal your wounded heart.
Won't you take it?
Ha?
You think this wound could
be healed with a rose, Orhan?
Alright, I know you
don't want that girl.
-But your mother
doesn't want me either.
If I make things right,
..will you believe me?
Can you convince your mother, Orhan?
If you believe me
...I can overcome all
the difficulties, Holofira.
But I have an important duty now.
A tough one. I may not come back.
But I don't want to leave a
wounded Holofira behind.
Holofira, will you forgive me?
I forgive you for now.
But I will never forgive you if
you don't come back, Orhan.
I will. I promise you.
I will be back, Holofira.
My Shahzade, horses are ready.
Stay safe.
GERM1YANOGLU SIN1RL / PAZAR
It is certain that Bala Hatun is
getting aware of some things.
The things she said that
day inviting you to the feast.
What do you think, Gonca?
Did Alaeddin spoke with his mother?
I don't know.
Bala Hatun is a good person.
She acted good towards me..
-As she did to everyone.
-Alright Gonca, I know you are secretive..
You are doing this for
duty, you know that right?
Tell me, how was the feast.
It was alright. Malhun Hatun
introduced Aysima Hatun to everyone.
Holofira was very upset about it.
She did not show it, however I understood.
How as Alaeddin towards you?
He did everything he
could to find a cure for you.
Gonca, it looks like you're
about to say something to me.
Mother, I've heard something.
Alaeddin Bey is coming!
Whatever, now go. We will talk later.
I've sent the last scout alps, Bayindir Bey.
We will find that Veysel dog before dark.
Inform everyone. The spies in Bursa..
And in Konya.
Look brother. When I catch that dog..
Bey, Veysel has been seen
going to the frontier marketplace.
Alps, to frontier marketplace. Come on.
Veysel.
Come on!
-Are you feeling better?
-Thanks to you, I am alright.
However, you still seem tired.
Gonca Hatun.
I've thought a lot last night.
Not only last night.
I've been thinking for a long time.
But I can not unsolve it.
There is nothing you can not solve.
This is not a wisdom matter.
This is not an issue to be
discussed here as well, however..
What are you saying? I
do not understand, scholar.
-Gonca.
-Yes?
I became sure when I found this.
Both sure of myself, and..
My Shahzade.
Whatever, we can talk later, alright?
-Alright.
-With your permission.
Bayindir Bey.
-My Shahzade.
-You were after Veysel?
Or?
My Shahzade, we've looked
everywhere. Tracks led us here.
-That dog is here.
-You say so?
We did not come across anyone suspicious.
What is happening, what are you doing?
-That Veysel dog.
-Alps, after him!
Catch him!
My Shahzade!
Come on! Catch him!
Catch him! He is running away!
You corrupted dog!
Enough!
What is this disgrace..
In my marketplace.
Alaeddin.
My Sultan! My Sultan!
My Sultan!
There is a grave matter
that I need to tell you.
Do not let them have me.
I ask for mercy.
You were their most trusted
man, Veysel. What happened?
Mehmed Bey! That dog is a spy!
He has been eating with us for
so long, now he is betraying us!
We will take him to Yenisehir.
Veysel will not go anywhere, Alaeddin Bey.
It is what Osman Bey ordered, Yakup Bey.
All orders beyond that is invalid.
This is Sultan Yakup you are facing, Alaeddin.
Know your place, then talk.
There is no need to talk, Mehmed Bey.
We will take this Veysel dog and leave.
-Come on alps.
-Alps!
No one can have the one
who takes shelter among us.
Sheathe your swords! I said sheathe!
Alaeddin. I will listen to Veysel first.
And you will not leave the marketplace.
I will decide what to do later.
-Kanyumaz.
-My Sultan.
-Bring Veysel.
-As you command, my Sultan.
Alps.
We will get off horses.
Because the route Alaeddin showed
tells us so, we will walk from here.
They won't hear the horses.
Make your preparations.
-Orhan.
-My Bey.
Come, son.
My son, your blood boils.
You are very eager to be a martyr.
However, this is not the time.
Your first task is to stay alive.
And keep your alps alive.
All of them are the sons of their mothers.
All of them are entrusted
to you from your father.
As you command, my Bey.
For what are we fighting
without taking a breather?
The dream of a magnificent
state is my heritage from my father.
And it is a heritage from
my father, to my sons.
My Bey. Your dream is my dream.
Your cause is my cause.
My blood boils, it is true.
However, we do not have
the lives to give out to dogs.
And I swear that we will raise..
The heritage from you with alps, with beys..
And with brothers, by our own efforts.
Step by step, life by life, we
will conquer this world, father.
As you've said before; "This
cause is greater than a lifetime."
Praise be!
Praise be.
Thank you, my son. My valiant, come here.
This is the route.
All right, my Bey.
You'll go this way.
-May your holy war be blessed.
-It is blessed, my Bey.
Alps, come on.
Our Shahzade will become a great Bey, my Bey.
We will be the last of Beys, Boran.
There will be many Sultans
from our generation after us.
-Many Sultans.
-Thank you, my Bey.
Say it without mumbling. What do you know?
My Sultan
The trap that was set against
you and the ambush of Mongols
were Osman Bey's plans.
Osman...!
Just so you get humiliated in front of Beys.
He did it to make himself look like a hero.
My Bey, let me...
Why would we believe you, Veysel?
Maybe there is another hostility between you.
And you're slandering because of that.
You're right, my Sultan.
But...
I'll show you something
important. If you let me...
This poison.
The poison he applied to the swords.
Kanyumaz.
So you're saying that
he poisoned himself first
and then found the cure and became the hero?
The scheme is huge Saadet Hatun.
Take this to the healer.
Let him take a look to
see if it's the same poison.
Yes, my Sultan.
There's one more thing, my Sultan.
Osman Bey
made a deal with Karacelasun.
They will meet in an inn in the east.
Fitnat.
Tell Ulgen to call Gonca.
If the real scheme was for you to come here...
...I'll cut your head, Veysel.
The truth will come out sooner or later.
Believe me, or
take my head.
At least
I'd be dying with the hands of
someone on the path of Haqq.
It's not a problem.
The fact that I haven't been able
to realize their treason all this time
makes my death justifiable.
-May I come in, my Bey?
-Come on in.
My Sultan, nokers were trying to
sneak in around the marketplace,
the other ones ran away, we caught him.
Mother, you called me.
Ulgen, you can leave.
Why was Alaeddin here?
We couldn't talk.
You were about to tell me something
before Alaeddin came, Gonca.
What happened in the palace? Did
Alaeddin declared his love for you?
No, mother.
Why did I want you to approach Alaeddin?
Why did I send you to that palace?
So that you would learn something.
What did you learn?
Osman Bey
is going to meet with
someone named Karacelasun.
They are a few people.
Alaeddin was going to make a route.
What are you saying, Gonca?
Then Veysel is right.
What happened, mother?
We need to tell this to your father.
Mother, mother?
My Allah, what am I going to do?
My Allah, please help
me. I don't know what to do.
Osman gave us gold and told us to attack Yakup.
He will give us the rest of
the gold when the job is done.
Who did Osman make a deal with?
With a dastard like you?
No, he made a deal with
our commander Karacelasun.
Now he is with him.
-May I come in, my Sultan?
-Come on in.
My Sultan, Veysel is right.
This is the same poison.
So you're saying that
Osman is working with you
he is giving you money.
Yes.
Where is Karacelasun?
-Let's go there and hear it from him.
-He's in the east,
...in the inn near Cinarli.
Alright.
Veysel.
I'll think about the issue first.
Then I'll make my decision.
Until then
Veysel will be our guest in our marketplace.
Be careful.
Kayis must not cause a conflict.
Keep your eyes on this dog.
Veysel is telling the truth.
Osman is going to Karacelasun.
With a few men.
People do not face their enemies
with a few men on their side.
They keep it secret.
Apparently he is after something.
Osman!
Osman!!
We poisoned the relationship between them.
This is important. Osman will
be Yakup's enemy forever now.
He will kill him sooner or later.
Soon, they will have their
own blood on their hands.
Yakup will kill Osman.
And we will kill the rest.
The weather is foggy now.
Fight, fight, fight.
Fight will change the balance
on these lands, Karacelasun.
The important thing is that there will be
no power left to stand against us in the end.
Fight.
You will keep bringing smokes
until it is not possible to see.
Don't worry.
My troops started moving.
Good..
Soon, their blood will be shed...
...for me to take my brother's revenge.
We will not wait anymore. Come on Alps!
Alaeddin Bey!
Don't... Be patient.
That man is a traitor, Gonca Hatun.
We cannot know what he is going to do.
My father does not trust him anyway.
Don't worry. -What if he believes him?
What if he believes him? Then
won't you regret standing before me?
Scholar. If I let you go now...
...will you go and raid my father's tent?
I cannot let that happen. Understand me.
My Shahzade. They are leaving.
Thanks to Allah, Yakup Bey.
Now give that traitor to us.
The traitor is your father!
Don't you mention my father's
name with your dirty tongue!
Brother! Brother, what are you doing?
Alaeddin! -Don't..
Don't... -Alaeddin!
Alaeddin! Brother!
Brother! -Enough!
Brother!
Alps! Arrest Alaeddin Bey and his Alps.
Father, don't... Father...
Father, don't.. -What are you doing, Gonca?
Mother...
You are making a mistake, Yakup Bey.
The man you are standing next to is a traitor!
You are believing the games of our enemies!
I am not going to learn what to
do and what not to do from you.
Yakup Bey! The man behind you
is the traitor we've been looking for!
Enough! Come on! Arrest them!
Yakup Bey... Yakup Bey!
Move, Cerkutay!
Gonca...
Don't...
Don't you feel upset.
Now those who have mercy in their hearts...
...cannot be on my side.
Step back!
My Shahzade... Order us,
and we will take you out of here.
They are too crowded, Baysungur.
We never shed our brothers' blood, and we
will never shed their blood. Do not resist.
-Kanyumaz. -My Sultan.
-Tell them to prepare our horses.
Yes my Sultan.
Let's see if there is betrayal...
...or not with our own eyes.
Are we ready, Boran?
We are my Bey, Biiznillah.
Alps surrounded the inn.
But... I don't understand why we
sent our Shahzade in advance, my Bey.
Our enemies are tough. He must
fight with the tough, so he can be one.
How can they lead our people if they
cannot lead the Alps and make a raid?
-Yes, my Bey.
-We will see his talent.
Now it is our turn.
What is this noise? Go and check.
Allah is The Greatest!
Osman's seed...
Is your father offering your
head instead of his own head?
Where is he?
The sword that took
your brother's head...
...is offered to you!
And it will slit your throat!
Young dog...
Was your father, the old wolf...
...afraid to face me?
He wanted blood to touch
the young wolf's teeth!
Osman... I was waiting for you.
So you were waiting for your death, huh?
Come... Now it is time to take your head.
Come at me.
What is this disgrace?
Did you start fighting when
you were working together?
What was the thing you could not share?
-Don't worry.
It will be done here.
Your end...
...has come just like him, Osman.
I know the traps
you set for me...
...the things you did with this dog...
...and everything you did!
What are you saying, Yakup Bey?
Huh? -Osman...
You sold me out to Yakup Bey, huh?
I thought we were going to work together.
What?!
Alps!
Contact: turkision@gmail.com